# **IMIEBO GODSON**

No.8 Idowu Akindele Crescent, Magodo Phase 2, Lagos. 07068161351

Email: Imiebo.godson@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/godson-imiebo-3b9878190/

Dev Blog: https://dev.to/imiebogodson

#### **OBJECTIVE**

To continually challenge myself within a reputable organization, where my professional skills, knowledge and experience will be effectively utilized, with the aim of collective goal achievement and self-improvement in order to achieve the organizational and individual goals and objectives.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.) in Electrical and Electronics Engineering, Second Class Honors (2018)

Kwara State University, Malete, Kwara State.

**O Levels**, English, Maths, Physics, Chemistry, Biology, Geography Effective International College, Ilorin, Kwara state.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

HNGi7 (Remote).

Frontend Engineer (March 2020 - August 2020)

Key Responsibilities:

- Used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build beautiful user interfaces that deliver a great user experience
- Collaborated with UI/UX designers and project managers to transform UI designs and mock-ups to pixel-perfect user interfaces
- Worked in a team that made use of the CRUD system to deliver time-sensitive projects that are used to solve reallife problems
- Contributed to open source projects on Github.

Nigerian Content Development and Monitoring Board (NCDMB), Bayelsa State.

Director of Finance and Personnel Management Office (November 2018 - December 2019) (NYSC)

## Technical Support Engineer

Key Responsibilities:

- Diagnosed and troubleshoot technical issues, including account setup and network configuration
- Researched and identified solutions to software and hardware issues
- Toke ownership of both internal and external Stakeholders' queries received; face-to-face, via phone or email correspondence and saw problems through to resolution
- Data management; backed up all essential data physically, on the hard-drive and on the cloud.
- Identified document priority levels and promptly forwarded high priority documents to the Director for action and promptly dispatched physically and via the electronic document management system(EDMS) platform put in place at the hoard
- Documented technical knowledge in the form of notes and manuals.

#### Key Achievements:

- Successfully tracked computer system issues through to resolution, within agreed time limits
- Talked both internal and external stakeholders through a series of actions, either via phone, email, or face-to-face, until they had solved a technical issue
- I was able to prioritize and manage several open issues at one time.
- Properly escalated unresolved issues to appropriate internal teams.

#### **Human Resource Assistant**

Key Responsibilities:

- Created and implemented the database for the 2018 staff learning plan using the Microsoft Excel.
- Logged all Learning and Development data to enable quick data call-up.
- Collected and sorted data from staff training needs assessment exercise to determine most appropriate learning intervention for individual staff during the preparation for the 2019 learning plan.
- Reviewed the progress of the 2018 learning plan from time to time during its implementation.

### Key Achievement:

Part of the Learning and Development team that successfully executed the 2018 Learning Plan.

Lubcon International, Kwara state.

### Assistant Maintenance Engineer (April 2015 - September 2015) (Internship)

Key Responsibilities:

- Troubleshooted and fixed electrical and mechanical faults in the factory.
- Performed daily maintenance checks on factory Machines before the start of work.

#### Key Achievements:

- Production was successfully increased by 12% during my time working in the maintenance team thanks to improvements made from on-floor observations.
- Researched and presented a detailed report to the factory manager on the most efficient options to start and
  operate the 3phase dc motors being used in the factory.

■Emotional intelligence ■Resilience.

Ministry of Energy, Kwara state.

### Electrical Maintenance Engineer (May 2014 - October 2014)

Key Responsibilities:

- Worked in a team to diagnose electrical faults that occurred in and around the office building.
- Procured electrical components to repair the faults diagnosed.
- Worked as a team to maintain, fix and replace street lights in the state.

### Key Achievement:

Worked as a team to successfully restored a damage electrical transformer and also, successfully presented a
graphical report of the operation.

#### **SKILLS**

- Prnactive and self-motivated.
- Knowledge of and keen interest Java, XML, JavaScript, HTML and CSS.
- Experience in web development.
- In-depth knowledge in MS Word, PowerPoint, Excel and Outlook.

- Communication and interpersonal skills
- Teamwork
- Technical writing and presentation

#### INTERESTS

During my personal time, I love to consume and create contents around software Development, personal growth. I enjoy reading books, listening to music, travelling, and spending time with family and friends. I also enjoy sports; basketball and soccer to be precise.

### REFERENCES

Available upon request